Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Suporte Admin Watch em kissasia.cam ou kisskh.org
How many times do I have to tell you?
Quantas vezes tenho de te dizer?
I'm sorry.
Lamento.
Don't be scared.
Não tenha medo.
Sorry.
Desculpa.
Why do you always make me do this?
Porque é que me faz sempre fazer isso?
I can't handle it, and then…
Não consigo lidar com isso, e depois...
I don't want this either, all right?
Eu também não quero isso, está bem?
How many years? Seven years…
Quantos anos? Sete anos…
Sorry, it's my fault.
Desculpe, a culpa é minha.
Jin Jin.
Jin Jin.
I can't face her.
Não consigo encará-la.
Hi.
Olá.
Mom, what're you up to? What took you so long to answer?
Mãe, o que estás a fazer? Porque demorou tanto tempo para responder?
Nothing, I was just busy.
Nada, só estava ocupado.
I'm at the hotel pool. Let me show you the night view.
Estou na piscina do hotel. Deixe-me mostrar-lhe a vista noturna.
It's stunning.
É impressionante.
I'm with An Chi.
Estou com o An Chi.
Hello, An Chi.
Olá An Chi.
Hello.
Olá.
You two be careful over there.
Vocês os dois tomem cuidado aí.
Don't worry. We're not kids anymore.
Não se preocupe. Já não somos crianças.
Mom, I've got to go. I just called to let you know I'm fine.
Mãe, preciso de ir. Só liguei para avisar que estou bem.
Okay.
Ok.
And I uploaded a new video on YouTube.
E carreguei um novo vídeo no YouTube.
Remember to hit like.
Lembre-se de gostar.
Okay.
Ok.
I'm hanging up. Bye.
Vou desligar. Tchau.
- Bye bye.
- Adeus, adeus.
JIN JIN
JIN JIN
Come join us!
Venha juntar-se a nós!
Hsin-yi, are you coming or not?
Hsin-yi, vens ou não?
Just tell your mom you're going to shoot videos with me.
Diz à tua mãe que vais gravar vídeos comigo.
We can split the earnings from videos and ads.
Podemos dividir os ganhos de vídeos e anúncios.
You can have fun and get paid. How cool is that?
Pode divertir-se e ainda ganhar dinheiro. Que giro!
Mom, I want to go to Benkha.
Mãe, quero ir a Benkha.
What for?
Para quê?
Jin Jin is there already.
Jin Jin já lá está.
She keeps asking me to join her.
Ela continua a pedir-me para acompanhá-la.
There's still time before school starts.
Ainda há tempo antes do início das aulas.
I can go on vacation.
Posso ir de férias.
And I can film some content with them and make some money.
E posso filmar algum conteúdo com eles e ganhar algum dinheiro.
I told you not to worry about money.
Eu disse-lhe para não se preocupar com dinheiro.
I'll handle it.
Eu trato disso.
But…
Mas…
- Go back inside. - Okay.
- Volte para dentro. - Certo.
I'll finish up here.
Vou terminar aqui.
SCAMMERS GO TO HELL
GOLPISTAS VÃO PARA O INFERNO
Officer Li!
Oficial Li!
PRESENT DAY, BENKHA
ATUALMENTE, BENKHA
You want me to steal a corpse?
Quer que eu roube um cadáver?
Mm.
Milímetros.
Please. You think too highly of me. I can't pull that off.
Por favor. Tem uma opinião muito elevada de mim. Eu não consigo fazer isso.
You can, Mr. Li.
Pode, Sr. Li.
Everyone in Chinatown knows you're the go-to-guy.
Toda a gente em Chinatown sabe que és o homem certo.
You're handsome and kind-hearted.
Você é bonito e bondoso.
Help us out.
Ajude-nos.
If you can meet this price,
Se puder atender a esse preço,
I'll do it.
Eu farei isso.
That's way too much.
Isto é demais.
No bargaining.
Sem regatear.
Don't give me that look.
Não me olhe assim.
Any idea how many people I'll have to bribe?
Alguma ideia de quantas pessoas terei de subornar?
Most of that will go to the morgue.
A maior parte irá para a morgue.
I'll barely have anything left.
Não me restará quase nada.
If you didn't look so desperate…
Se não parecesse tão desesperado...
Whatever. You've got time to think it over.
Tanto faz. Tem tempo para pensar.
Wait, fine…
Espera, tudo bem…
We'll pay.
Nós pagaremos.
We'll find the money.
Nós encontraremos o dinheiro.
We will.
Vamos.
Good.
Bom.
Come up with the money quickly.
Arranje o dinheiro rapidamente.
The body will be cremated in 72 hours.
O corpo será cremado dentro de 72 horas.
Okay?
Ok?
Don't you want to know why we want to steal Chang Shih-kai's corpse?
Não quer saber porque queremos roubar o cadáver de Chang Shih-kai?
If I ask you, will you tell me?
Se eu te perguntar, dizes-me?
If we do, can you lower the price?
Se fizermos isso, pode baixar o preço?
What do you think?
O que acha?
In any case,
Em todo o caso,
you pay the money
você paga o dinheiro
and I'll do the job.
e eu farei o trabalho.
All right, you can go now.
Tudo bem, pode ir agora.
See yourselves out.
Saiam daqui.
Get the money quick. Time's running out.
Receba o dinheiro rápido. O tempo está a esgotar-se.
Who is it?
Quem é?
Hsiang.
Hsiang.
Stop coming here.
Deixe de vir aqui.
- Sorry. - Don't apologize to me.
- Desculpe. - Não me desculpe.
If you're really sorry, tell them to pay up.
Se realmente sente muito, diga-lhes para pagarem.
I thought of you as a friend.
Pensei em ti como um amigo.
So I listened to you and bought that life insurance for my mom.
Então ouvi-te e comprei aquele seguro de vida para a minha mãe.
Now my mother's in the ICU and desperately needs the money!
Agora a minha mãe está na UCI e precisa desesperadamente do dinheiro!
But your company won't pay out!
Mas a sua empresa não vai pagar!
I tried to get it back
Eu tentei recuperá-lo
but they said it's an investment-based policy and it's all gone!
mas disseram que é uma política baseada em investimentos e está tudo acabado!
You know what you are?
Sabe o que é?
- You're a scammer! - I'll make it up to you. Here's some…
- Você é um burlão! - Vou compensar-te. Aqui fica um pouco...
- No, I don't want it! - Don't be so mean.
- Não, não quero! - Não seja tão mau.
- I'm suing your company! - She has it hard too.
- Vou processar a sua empresa! - Ela também está a passar por dificuldades.
Karma will get you!
O karma vai apanhá-lo!
Chao Ching, ignore him. He doesn't mean it.
Chao Ching, ignore-o. Ele não quis dizer isso.
She scammed us.
Ela enganou-nos.
Don't say that.
Não diga isso.
- It's not her fault. - No?
- A culpa não é dela. - Não?
Karma will get her! Serves her right!
O karma vai acabar com ela! Bem feito para ela!
Ching, there you are.
Ching, aí estás tu.
Have a seat.
Sente-se.
Things must be tough for you lately.
As coisas devem estar difíceis para si ultimamente.
I'm fine.
Estou bem.
Why don't I transfer your clients to Hsiao-chou for the time being?
Porque não transfiro os seus clientes para Hsiao-chou por enquanto?
I found those clients. Why should I give them to her?
Eu encontrei esses clientes. Por que razão devo entregá-los a ela?
Precisely because you worked so hard to get those clients.
Precisamente porque trabalhou muito para conseguir esses clientes.
We should do our best to keep them.
Devemos fazer o nosso melhor para os manter.
I'm worried you're spreading yourself too thin,
Estou preocupado que se esteja a espalhar muito,
so I want Hsiao-chou to help you out.
então quero que o Hsiao-chou o ajude.
Without any clients, how will I reach my sales target?
Sem clientes, como atingirei o meu objetivo de vendas?
Don't worry about that. The company's taken it into account.
Não se preocupe com isso. A empresa teve isso em consideração.
With your family's situation, the lawsuit,
Com a situação da sua família, o processo,
and dealing with those pesky reporters,
e lidar com aqueles repórteres irritantes,
it must be hard to focus.
deve ser difícil concentrar-se.
So we've decided to transfer you to General Affairs.
Decidimos então transferi-lo para Assuntos Gerais.
This will reduce your workload.
Isso reduzirá a sua carga de trabalho.
You're demoting me?
Está a me rebaixando?
How will I survive on that salary?
Como vou sobreviver com este salário?
Don't worry.
Não te preocupes.
Once this matter is over, you can transfer right back.
Quando este assunto estiver resolvido, poderá voltar imediatamente.
I need money now more than ever.
Preciso de dinheiro agora mais do que nunca.
And the company needs sales more than ever.
E a empresa precisa de vendas mais do que nunca.
The company always needs sales.
A empresa precisa sempre de vendas.
To reach my sales targets these past few years,
Para atingir os meus objetivos de vendas nos últimos anos,
I sold insurance policies to many of my friends and family.
Vendi apólices de seguro a muitos amigos e familiares.
But the company refused to pay up.
Mas a empresa recusou-se a pagar.
Now everyone calls me a scammer.
Agora toda a gente me chama de golpista.
I gave a lot to this company.
Eu dei muito a esta empresa.
Now I'm being transferred to General Affairs?
Agora estou a ser transferido para Assuntos Gerais?
Ching,
Ching,
that all happened before I joined the company,
tudo isto aconteceu antes de eu entrar na empresa,
so I know nothing about it.
por isso não sei nada sobre isso.
Besides, all of our products comply with legal regulations now.
Além disso, todos os nossos produtos estão agora em conformidade com as normas legais.
- Are you saying - This--
- Está a dizer - Isso--
the old products were illegal?
os produtos antigos eram ilegais?
Don't take it out on me.
Não desconte em mim.
The company decided to transfer you.
A empresa decidiu transferi-lo.
It had nothing to do with me.
Não teve nada a ver comigo.
To put it bluntly, you want me to resign.
Para ser franco, quer que eu me demita.
That's nonsense.
Isto é um absurdo.
Look at all that's happening to you right now.
Veja tudo o que lhe está a acontecer agora.
It must be hard to focus on your job.
Deve ser difícil concentrar-se no trabalho.
And our company has always been very accommodating.
E a nossa empresa foi sempre muito recetiva.
Think about it some more.
Pense um pouco mais sobre o assunto.
Where will you find another company
Onde encontrará outra empresa
as good as this one?
tão bom como este?
You know I'm right.
Sabe que estou certo.
What are you doing?
O que estás a fazer?
The manager asked me to sort your client files.
O gerente pediu-me para organizar os seus ficheiros de clientes.
Hsiao-chou.
Hsiao-chou.
- Yes? - Come here.
- Sim? - Vem cá.
Sorry.
Desculpa.
- Do it later. - Didn't you tell Ching?
- Faça-o depois. - Não disseste ao Ching?
It was so awkward.
Foi tão estranho.
Did you just get back?
Acabou de voltar?
Traffic was terrible.
O trânsito estava terrível.
I was swamped with work. No time to pick you up.
Eu estava atolado de trabalho. Não tive tempo de te ir buscar.
You don't need to take me to the airport tomorrow.
Não precisa de me levar ao aeroporto amanhã.
I don't trust a caregiver with Jin Jin.
Não confio num cuidador com Jin Jin.
I'll go and renew my visa.
Vou renovar o meu visto.
I'll just get a taxi and head over from there.
Vou apanhar um táxi e ir até lá.
Oh, okay.
Oh, tudo bem.
I'll just drop my things off.
Vou só deixar lá as minhas coisas.
Don't you ever clean?
Nunca limpa?
I've been pretty busy lately.
Tenho estado muito ocupado ultimamente.
- Hey. - I'm gonna shower.
- Ei. - Vou tomar banho.
I have a meeting later.
Tenho uma reunião mais logo.
TAIWAN WATER CORP.
CORP. DE ÁGUAS DE TAIWAN
APBANK
APBANK
QIAN'AN RD., TAIPEI
Estrada Qian'an, Taipé
QIONGYU ST., TAIPEI
Rua QIONGYU, TAIPEI
TOTAL PAYABLE: 36,875 TWD
TOTAL A PAGAR: 36.875 TWD
Hey.
Olá.
Look, I have to entertain clients tonight.
Olha, tenho de entreter clientes esta noite.
You're on your own tonight.
Está sozinho esta noite.
Don't wait for me.
Não espere por mim.
Did you hear me?
Você ouviu-me?
I heard you.
Eu ouvi-te.
TING: I'M HEADING OUT
TING: ESTOU A SAIR
ENTER PASSCODE
DIGITE A SENHA
Miss, are you getting out here?
Menina, a senhora vai sair daqui?
QIONGYU ST., TAIPEI
Rua QIONGYU, TAIPEI
Please take me to Qiongyu Street in Tianmu.
Por favor, leve-me à Rua Qiongyu, em Tianmu.
CHOU SHU-TING ACADEMIC ACHIEVEMENT AWARD
PRÉMIO DE REALIZAÇÃO ACADÉMICA CHOU SHU-TING
KUO CHIH-CHIEH'S CAMPAIGN STAFF MEMBER GOES VIRAL FOR HER BEAUTY
FUNCIONÁRIA DA CAMPANHA DE KUO CHIH-CHIEH TORNA- SE VIRAL PELA SUA BELEZA
CHOU SHU-TING ADMITS POLITICS IS STRESSFUL,
CHOU SHU-TING ADMITE QUE A POLÍTICA É ESTRESSANTE,
SUSPENDS WORK FOR A YEAR-LONG STUDY TOUR
SUSPENDE TRABALHO PARA UMA VIAGEM DE ESTUDO DE UM ANO
I'm Hsu Yung, from Super News. I'm doing an exclusive on fraud…
Sou o Hsu Yung, da Super News. Estou a fazer uma reportagem exclusiva sobre fraudes...
Hello?
Olá?
Is this Hsu Yung, the reporter for Super News?
Será este Hsu Yung, o repórter da Super News?
It's Chao Ching.
É o Chao Ching.
I'm back in Taiwan.
Estou de volta a Taiwan.
Were you drinking again?
Estava a beber de novo?
Sentenced to death.
Condenado à morte.
I wonder what'll happen to the civil damages.
Gostaria de saber o que acontecerá aos danos civis.
- I'm feeling down. - Give me a hand.
- Estou a sentir-me mal. - Dê-me uma mão.
Come and give me a hand.
Venha e dê-me uma mão.
Oh.
Oh.
- Like this? - Yes.
- Assim? - Sim.
One, two, three.
Um, dois, três.
Hey.
Olá.
Sorry.
Desculpa.
Help me contact a medical flight.
Ajude-me a entrar em contacto com um voo médico.
I'm going to send Jin Jin back to Taiwan in a few months.
Vou mandar o Jin Jin de volta para Taiwan daqui a uns meses.
No problem. I'll arrange it right away.
Sem problemas. Vou tratar disso agora mesmo.
You haven't given me this month's living expenses yet.
Ainda não me deu as despesas de vida deste mês.
Can we talk about this?
Podemos falar sobre isso?
Jin Jin made a lot from that sponsored content.
Jin Jin lucrou muito com este conteúdo patrocinado.
I don't think I need to keep paying.
Acho que não preciso de continuar a pagar.
- I have lots of expenses myself. - What kind of expenses?
- Eu próprio tenho muitas despesas. - Que tipo de despesas?
I'm doing business with a friend.
Estou a fazer negócios com um amigo.
I take care of all our household expenses in Taiwan, don't I?
Eu trato de todas as despesas da nossa casa em Taiwan, não é?
Don't I contribute enough?
Não contribuo o suficiente?
I'm heading back to Taiwan tomorrow.
Vou regressar a Taiwan amanhã.
- When will you be back? - We'll see.
- Quando regressa? - Vamos ver.
Doubt I'll be in Southeast Asia for work anytime soon.
Duvido que esteja no Sudeste Asiático em trabalho em breve.
So you're saying
Então está a dizer
I won't be seeing you or any money?
Não te vou ver nem ganhar dinheiro?
That's not what I said. Or what I meant.
Não foi isso que eu disse. Nem o que eu quis dizer.
I knew you'd get upset.
Eu sabia que ias ficar chateado.
I think we should make plans for the future.
Acho que devemos fazer planos para o futuro.
He's dead now.
Ele está morto agora.
Just let things come to an end.
Deixe apenas as coisas chegarem ao fim.
We need to let go and stop punishing ourselves.
We need to let go and stop punishing ourselves.
We should move on.
We should move on.
I think we should move on too.
I think we should move on too.
That's right.
That's right.
So, can we discuss what I mentioned last time?
So, can we discuss what I mentioned last time?
Sure.
Claro.
Good. I want to make things clear.
Good. I want to make things clear.
- So if we separate in the future-- - Not in front of Jin Jin.
- So if we separate in the future-- - Not in front of Jin Jin.
Okay, not now.
Okay, not now.
- I'll do it. - No, I'll do it myself.
- I'll do it. - No, I'll do it myself.
Okay, then let's talk at my hotel.
Okay, then let's talk at my hotel.
Hua Hsin!
Hua Hsin!
- Hua Hsin makes dirty money! - You scammers!
- Hua Hsin makes dirty money! - You scammers!
- Swindlers! - Scammers!
- Swindlers! - Scammers!
- You exploit people! - Pay us back!
- You exploit people! - Pay us back!
- Hua Hsin, pay up! - Scammers, pay up!
- Hua Hsin, pay up! - Scammers, pay up!
- Hua Hsin, give us back our money!
- Hua Hsin, give us back our money!
Pay us back!
Pay us back!
- Come out and face us! - Scammers!
- Come out and face us! - Scammers!
- Hua Hsin, pay us back!
- Hua Hsin, pay us back!
Ching, you have a guest.
Ching, you have a guest.
Yes, I know your show is incredible at exposés.
Yes, I know your show is incredible at exposés.
My business card. Hsu Yung, Super News.
My business card. Hsu Yung, Super News.
You can just call me Yung.
You can just call me Yung.
To help Super News get the truth, I go super.
To help Super News get the truth, I go super.
Ching, there you are.
Ching, there you are.
- Mr. Hsu. - Ching.
- Mr. Hsu. - Ching.
Congratulations. Justice has finally been served.
Congratulations. Justice has finally been served.
By the way,
By the way,
Mr. Hsu said you two have something to discuss today.
Mr. Hsu said you two have something to discuss today.
Yes. But first, I have to tender my resignation.
Yes. But first, I have to tender my resignation.
What?
O quê?
Resignation?
Resignation?
But…
But…
You're doing great. Why would you resign?
You're doing great. Why would you resign?
I feel the company's been too accommodating.
I feel the company's been too accommodating.
- I don't want to implicate the company. - How can you say that?
- I don't want to implicate the company. - How can you say that?
We're a family.
We're a family.
And the company has always had your back.
And the company has always had your back.
Hey.
Olá.
Don't rush things.
Don't rush things.
Let's talk about it.
Let's talk about it.
Let's talk.
Let's talk.
Ms. Chou.
Ms. Chou.
Hsiao-chou, she called for you.
Hsiao-chou, she called for you.
- Mr. Hsu, please give me a moment. - Take your time.
- Mr. Hsu, please give me a moment. - Take your time.
Take good care of Mr. Hsu for me.
Take good care of Mr. Hsu for me.
Oh, remember to make some coffee.
Oh, remember to make some coffee.
Go and make some coffee.
Go and make some coffee.
- Mr. Hsu. Have a seat. - Yes, yes.
- Mr. Hsu. Have a seat. - Yes, yes.
On the left.
On the left.
Sit anywhere you like.
Sit anywhere you like.
I'm gonna take a shower.
I'm gonna take a shower.
Do you remember?
Do you remember?
I told you before
I told you before
how I wanted a fresh start
how I wanted a fresh start
once the lawsuit was over.
once the lawsuit was over.
Did you?
Did you?
When was that?
When was that?
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
Anyway, now everything's wrapped up,
Anyway, now everything's wrapped up,
I don't want to drag things on.
I don't want to drag things on.
I'm glad you think that way.
I'm glad you think that way.
At least Jin Jin won't suffer so much.
At least Jin Jin won't suffer so much.
The sooner her suffering ends, the better for us, no?
The sooner her suffering ends, the better for us, no?
What do you mean?
What do you mean?
Aren't we talking about turning off Jin Jin's life support?
Aren't we talking about turning off Jin Jin's life support?
What were you talking about?
What were you talking about?
For years, we've been apart more often than not.
For years, we've been apart more often than not.
We're married in name only.
We're married in name only.
So you're aware?
So you're aware?
You finally realized.
You finally realized.
Let's get divorced.
Let's get divorced.
Divorced?
Divorced?
Fine.
Bom.
What about Jin Jin?
What about Jin Jin?
I'll take care of Jin Jin.
I'll take care of Jin Jin.
Good. It's better for a child to be with their mother.
Ótimo. É melhor para uma criança estar com a mãe.
We'll do the paperwork back in Taiwan.
Nós faremos a papelada em Taiwan.
Not so fast. I have a few conditions.
Calma. Tenho algumas condições.
What conditions?
Quais as condições?
Ching, what do you want to talk to that reporter for?
Ching, sobre o que quer falar com aquele repórter?
He wants to interview me.
Ele quer entrevistar-me.
Don't you always refuse interviews?
Não recusa sempre as entrevistas?
I need the money.
Preciso do dinheiro.
That's true.
Isso é verdade.
Super News has really high ratings.
O Super News tem audiências muito elevadas.
Remember to get a good price.
Lembre-se de conseguir um bom preço.
- You must be having a hard time lately. - What? No.
- Deve estar a passar por momentos difíceis ultimamente. - O quê? Não.
Ever since you transferred me to General Affairs,
Desde que me transferiu para Assuntos Gerais,
I've had a lot of time on my hands at work.
Tenho tido muito tempo livre no trabalho.
Sometimes, I'd get so bored
Às vezes ficava tão aborrecido
that I'd dig out the company's past internal records
que iria desenterrar os registos internos anteriores da empresa
for a look.
para dar uma vista de olhos.
I discovered that Fukang Universal Life Insurance
Descobri que a Fukang Universal Life Insurance
was deemed high-risk.
foi considerado de alto risco.
But when we promoted it externally,
Mas quando o promovemos externamente,
we labeled it a low-risk product.
rotulamos como um produto de baixo risco.
And customers were never told of the possibility of loss of capital.
E os clientes nunca foram informados da possibilidade de perda de capital.
This is straight-up fraud.
Isto é uma fraude descarada.
What fraud? Be careful about what you say.
Que fraude? Cuidado com o que diz.
- This was before I joined-- - I know.
- Isso foi antes de eu entrar... - Eu sei.
That was before you joined the company.
Isso foi antes de entrar na empresa.
But now, you'll have to take all the blame.
Mas agora terá de assumir toda a culpa.
It's so unfair on you.
É tão injusto para si.
That's why I'll go on that show
É por isso que vou àquele concerto
and apologize to everyone I scammed.
e peço desculpa a todos os que enganei.
I'm sure my unethical conduct
Tenho a certeza de que a minha conduta pouco ética
- led to my daughter's tragic death. - No.
- levou à morte trágica da minha filha. - Não.
- Chao Ching-- - It's my karma.
- Chao Ching-- - É o meu karma.
Chao Ching, what are you talking about?
Chao Ching, do que é que está a falar?
Do you know how much this'll affect the company
Sabe o quanto isso afetará a empresa
if you spout this crap on TV?
se disser essa porcaria na TV?
Yes, I know.
Sim, sei.
That's why I came in today to resign.
Foi por isso que vim hoje para me demitir.
But--
Mas--
I don't want to implicate the company.
Não quero implicar a empresa.
The money in our joint account is from fundraisers for Jin Jin,
O dinheiro na nossa conta conjunta provém de angariações de fundos para Jin Jin,
so it should go towards for her expenses.
então deveria ser utilizado para cobrir as despesas dela.
How can we do that?
Como podemos fazer isso?
That's a joint account.
Esta é uma conta conjunta.
By law, we should split it, right?
Por lei, devemos dividir, certo?
Then let's follow the law.
Então vamos seguir a lei.
This is Hsiao-pao when he was born.
Este é Hsiao-pao quando nasceu.
Haven't you always wanted a son?
Sempre quis ter um filho, não é?
His nose is just like yours.
O nariz dele é igual ao teu.
This is him at one year old out shopping with his mother.
Este é ele com um ano de idade a fazer compras com a mãe.
He doesn't make a fuss. So cute.
Ele não faz alarido. É tão fofinho.
And this is him at two years old.
E este é ele com dois anos de idade.
You guys celebrated his birthday at the amusement park.
Vocês celebraram o aniversário dele no parque de diversões.
He's a Sagittarius just like you.
Ele é de Sagitário, tal como você.
He'll grow up to be a scumbag too.
Ele vai crescer e tornar-se um canalha também.
Hsiao-pao is so cute.
Hsiao-pao é tão fofinho.
At five or six years old,
Aos cinco ou seis anos de idade,
he'll start elementary school.
ele vai começar o ensino fundamental.
The apartment you bought is in Tianmu.
O apartamento que comprou fica em Tianmu.
Near an international school, no?
Perto de uma escola internacional, não?
I'll pay him a visit when I have time.
Farei uma visita a ele quando tiver tempo.
When he's 12 or 13 in a few years, he'll go online.
Quando tiver 12 ou 13 anos, daqui a alguns anos, estará online.
Then he'll learn that his sister is a famous YouTuber.
Depois descobrirá que a sua irmã é uma YouTuber famosa.
Since I took over, I think we've reached 500,000 subscribers.
Desde que assumi o cargo, penso que atingimos os 500.000 assinantes.
And then,
E então,
I'll tell the whole world
Eu contarei ao mundo inteiro
that his father is a scumbag and his mother is a homewrecker.
que o seu pai é um canalha e a sua mãe é uma destruidora de lares.
By the way,
Já agora,
will this affect Kuo Chih-chieh's election prospects?
afetará as perspetivas eleitorais de Kuo Chih-chieh?
If you want to resign,
Se quiser renunciar,
you need to sign a non-disclosure agreement.
precisa de assinar um acordo de confidencialidade.
- A non-disclosure agreement? - Yes!
- Um acordo de confidencialidade? - Sim!
After you sign it,
Depois de assinar,
you can't tell anyone about anything related to the company.
não pode contar a ninguém sobre nada relacionado com a empresa.
Do I have to sign it?
Tenho de assinar?
Of course.
Claro.
What if I don't sign it?
E se não assinar?
That's…
Isto é…
What exactly do you want?
O que quer exatamente?
DIVORCE AGREEMENT
ACORDO DE DIVÓRCIO
I want all of your money
Eu quero todo o seu dinheiro
and the apartment in Tianmu.
e o apartamento em Tianmu.
Well,
Bem,
if you sign it,
se assinar,
the company will compensate you.
a empresa irá compensá-lo.
How much?
Quanto?
I'll try my best, okay? I'll try my best!
Vou dar o meu melhor, ok? Vou dar o meu melhor!
Remember to get a good price.
Lembre-se de conseguir um bom preço.
You said before
Você disse antes
that Super News has really high ratings.
que o Super News tem audiências realmente elevadas.
Hi.
Olá.
Please sign here.
Assine aqui, por favor.
The apartment is in her name.
O apartamento está em nome dela.
- She won't agree. - She will agree
- Ela não vai concordar. - Ela vai concordar.
because she's also a mother now.
porque ela também é mãe agora.
For her child's sake, she'll compromise.
Pelo bem do filho, ela fará um acordo.
I have to discuss it with her back in Taipei.
Tenho de discutir isso com ela em Taipé.
- I'll also need a lawyer-- - I don't have time for that.
- Também vou precisar de um advogado-- - Não tenho tempo para isso.
Do everything I've told you as soon as possible.
Faça tudo o que eu disse o mais rapidamente possível.
Sign this agreement tonight and send it to me.
Assine este acordo esta noite e envie-mo.
Did you hear me?
Você ouviu-me?
Yes.
Sim.
Her signature too.
A assinatura dela também.
Take care of yourself for the next two days.
Cuide-se nos próximos dois dias.
If you get into an accident on the road
Se sofrer um acidente na estrada
or get hit by a car,
ou ser atropelado por um automóvel,
I'm still your insurance beneficiary.
Continuo a ser o seu beneficiário do seguro.
Didn't you say not to touch Jin Jin's money?
Não disse para não tocar no dinheiro do Jin Jin?
It's my ex-husband's.
É do meu ex-marido.
We got divorced.
Nós divorciamo-nos.
Let's make a to-do list.
Vamos fazer uma lista de tarefas.
Then we'll see what's missing and figure it out.
Depois veremos o que está a faltar e descobriremos.
First is money.
O primeiro é o dinheiro.
Chang Shih-kai.
Chang Shih-kai.
Where to hide him?
Onde escondê-lo?
Transport.
Transporte.
We need to control him once we have him.
Precisamos de o controlar quando o temos.
TO-DO LIST: MONEY, CHANG SHIH-KAI, LOCATION, TRANSPORT, CONTROL
LISTA DE TAREFAS: DINHEIRO, CHANG SHIH-KAI, LOCALIZAÇÃO, TRANSPORTES, CONTROLO
We have to pay Mr. Li tonight.
Temos de pagar ao Sr. Li esta noite.
Do you think we can trust him?
Acha que podemos confiar nele?
I've asked around.
Perguntei por aí.
As long as he's paid, he gets the job done.
Desde que seja pago, ele faz o trabalho.
He has an excellent reputation.
Tem uma excelente reputação.
CHANG SHIH-KAI
CHANG SHIH-KAI
Here.
Aqui.
Okay.
Ok.
Up. Okay.
Para cima. Ok.
That's it. Okay.
É por aí. Certo.
CHANG SHIH-KAI
CHANG SHIH-KAI
All done.
Tudo pronto.
After we get Chang Shih-kai,
Depois de termos apanhado Chang Shih-kai,
where should we hide him?
onde devemos escondê-lo?
This place is big and seems private enough.
Este lugar é grande e parece bastante privado.
This side is Pong's pharmacy.
Este lado é a farmácia do Pong.
On the left is a bar.
À esquerda há um bar.
Wonder how soundproof it is.
Imagino o quão à prova de som é.
Fuck you!
Foda-se!
- Hey! - Hi!
- Olá!
Hey! You came!
Ei! Você veio!
CAN'T HEAR ANYTHING
NÃO CONSIGO OUVIR NADA
Hui-chun!
Hui-chun!
Hi, Pong.
Olá Pong.
What happened?
O que aconteceu?
I hear Hui-chun screaming all the time.
Ouço Hui-chun a gritar o tempo todo.
I don't know what happened.
Não sei o que aconteceu.
What is it, Pong?
O que é isto, Pong?
What happened?
O que aconteceu?
Nothing.
Nada.
Okay.
Ok.
Good night.
Boa noite.
The bar is fine.
O bar está ótimo.
The last thing is Pong's pharmacy.
A última coisa é a farmácia do Pong.
What do we do? That'll cost a ton of money.
O que fazemos? Isso vai custar uma fortuna.
We're burning through it too quickly.
Estamos a consumir tudo muito rápido.
Now we…
Agora nós…
Hey, Pong.
Olá Pong.
Hey.
Olá.
I've got a cheap alternative.
Tenho uma alternativa barata.
Pong!
Pong!
- No-- - It's okay. Don't worry. Just a few days.
- Não... - Está bem. Não se preocupe. Só mais uns dias.
Please take care of my store for me, okay?
Por favor, trate da minha loja por mim, ok?
- Okay. - Thank you.
- Ok. - Obrigado.
Are you sure about this?
Tem certeza disso?
I've asked.
Eu perguntei.
Drug offenses just get a few days in detention here.
Aqui, os crimes relacionados com drogas só podem resultar em alguns dias de detenção.
All clear. Let's go. Okay.
Tudo bem. Vamos lá. Certo.
Let's go.
Vamos.
Let's get started.
Vamos começar.
LOCATION
LOCALIZAÇÃO
TRANSPORT
TRANSPORTE
Getting there is fine.
Chegar lá é ótimo.
Bringing him back will be tricky.
Trazê-lo de volta será complicado.
There's got to be a way.
Tem de haver um jeito.
ESTAZOLAM
ESTAZOLAM
More, more, more.
Mais, mais, mais.
How about now?
Que tal agora?
Up, up.
Para cima, para cima.
Everything is ready.
Tudo está pronto.
We can begin.
Podemos começar.
LOCATION, TRANSPORT, CONTROL
LOCALIZAÇÃO, TRANSPORTES, CONTROLO
AN EYE FOR AN EYE, A TOOTH FOR A TOOTH
OLHO POR OLHO, DENTE POR DENTE
Is anyone here?
Está alguém aqui?
What is it?
O que é?
Go!
Ir!
Go, go!
Vai, vai!
I want a glass of juice.
Quero um copo de sumo.
No. We're closed already.
Não. Já estamos fechados.
This. Orange juice.
Isto. Sumo de laranja.
- No. - Drink.
- Não. - Beba.
Tell him to quiet down.
Diga-lhe para ficar quieto.
- Okay. Go. - Cup.
- Ok. Ir. - Taça.
Cup!
Taça!
Hurry, I'm thirsty.
Depressa, tenho sede.
Go, go, go.
Vai! Vai! Vai.
Where's the ice?
Onde está o gelo?
Ice!
Gelo!
I want to drink something cold with ice.
Quero beber algo gelado com gelo.
Hey!
Olá!
What the hell?
Que raio?
- Okay. - What kind of place doesn’t use ice?
- Certo. - Que tipo de local não utiliza gelo?
How am I supposed to drink this? Who sells drinks without ice?
Como vou beber isto? Quem vende bebidas sem gelo?
Hey! I want to drink something cold!
Ei! Quero beber algo gelado!
I'm thirsty!
Tenho sede!
Hurry up, I’m thirsty.
Depressa, tenho sede.
Thank you.
Obrigado.
Bye!
Adeus!
Oh, my God.
Oh meu Deus.
Think he'll get diarrhea?
Acha que ele vai ter diarreia?
Who cares?
Quem se importa?
I can't. This kind of music makes me cry.
Não consigo. Este tipo de música faz-me chorar.
Why would a song make you cry?
Porque é que uma música o faria chorar?
I hardly ever see you cry.
Quase nunca te vejo chorar.
Of course I cry.
Claro que choro.
When?
Quando?
When Hsin-yi died.
Quando Hsin-yi morreu.
And…
E…
when my husband died.
quando o meu marido morreu.
I rarely hear you talk about your husband.
Raramente a ouço falar sobre o seu marido.
It wasn't some passionate romance. It's not worth mentioning.
Não foi um romance apaixonado. Não vale a pena referir.
How did you two meet?
Como é que vocês os dois se conheceram?
He used to come to Kuala Lumpur for work.
Costumava vir para Kuala Lumpur para trabalhar.
I thought he was quite nice.
Achei-o bem legal.
He gave me a sense of security.
Ele deu-me uma sensação de segurança.
And then we got together.
E então reunimo-nos.
And then?
E então?
I dropped everything, got married and moved to Taiwan.
Deixei tudo, casei e mudei-me para Taiwan.
Then what happened?
Então o que aconteceu?
I had Hsin-yi and the three of us lived our lives.
Eu tive Hsin-yi e nós os três vivemos as nossas vidas.
That's it.
É isso.
How did he die?
Como morreu?
Cancer.
Cancro.
Ever since I learned about the Goddess,
Desde que aprendi sobre a Deusa,
the person I wanted to revive the most wasn't Hsin-yi.
a pessoa que eu mais queria reviver não era Hsin-yi.
It was my husband.
Era o meu marido.
Why not Hsin-yi?
Por que não Hsin-yi?
Even if she was revived, she'd only have seven days.
Mesmo que fosse reanimada, teria apenas sete dias.
The burden of knowing your death is imminent
O fardo de saber que a sua morte é iminente
is too cruel…
é muito cruel…
for a young girl.
para uma jovem.
But my husband was different. He was amazing.
Mas o meu marido era diferente. Ele era incrível.
When he found out he had cancer,
Quando descobriu que tinha cancro,
the doctor told him he had three months left.
o médico disse que faltavam três meses para ele nascer.
He actually kept it from me.
Na verdade, ele escondeu-o de mim.
He happily got on with life
Seguiu feliz com a vida
as if nothing had happened.
como se nada tivesse acontecido.
Then one day, he passed out at home.
Então, um dia, desmaiou em casa.
I took him to the hospital and found out.
Levei-o ao hospital e descobri.
After that,
Depois disso,
he never
ele nunca
woke up again.
acordei novamente.
I didn't get the chance to speak to him one last time.
Não tive oportunidade de falar com ele uma última vez.
Why did he keep it from you?
Por que razão ele lhe escondeu isso?
He was probably worried I couldn't take it.
Provavelmente estava preocupado que eu não aguentasse.
He kept working hard,
Ele continuou a trabalhar duro,
hoping to save enough money for me and Hsin-yi.
esperando poupar dinheiro suficiente para mim e para o Hsin-yi.
So he refused treatment.
Depois recusou o tratamento.
Your husband was such a good man.
O seu marido era um homem tão bom.
But I couldn't fulfill his wishes.
Mas não consegui realizar os seus desejos.
When he was dying,
Quando estava a morrer,
I spent all of our money on his treatment.
Gastei todo o nosso dinheiro no tratamento dele.
Even my mother-in-law urged me not to waste money.
Até a minha sogra me pediu para não desperdiçar dinheiro.
The doctor said his chances were slim.
O médico disse que as suas hipóteses eram pequenas.
But I wouldn't listen.
Mas eu não quis ouvir.
I wanted him to wake up.
Eu queria que ele acordasse.
If he woke up,
Se ele acordasse,
what would you say to him?
o que lhe diria?
I'd probably yell at him for a bit.
Provavelmente gritaria com ele um pouco.
If you can't help them, let them die.
Se não os pode ajudar, deixe-os morrer.
The Goddess says she cannot feel the living's longing for him
A Deusa diz que não consegue sentir a saudade dos vivos por ele
and cannot resurrect him.
e não pode ressuscitá-lo.
What?
O quê?
How can that be?
Como pode ser?
Please leave.
Por favor, vá-se embora.
Goddess,
Deusa,
please, try--
por favor, tente--
Sorry.
Desculpa.
I got our daughter killed.
Eu fiz com que a nossa filha fosse morta.
Back then,
Naquela época,
if I had listened to you
se eu te tivesse escutado
and not spent all that money,
e não gastei todo esse dinheiro,
our lives wouldn't have been so tough…
as nossas vidas não teriam sido tão difíceis…
and this wouldn't have happened to Hsin-yi.
e isso não teria acontecido com Hsin-yi.
I'm so scared.
Tenho tanto medo.
That's why
É por isso
I need you to wake up.
Preciso que acorde.
So I can say goodbye to you properly.
Para que me possa despedir de si adequadamente.
I'm all on my own now.
Estou sozinho agora.
I miss you so much.
Tenho tantas saudades tuas.